Guide to the Time Inc. People Publishing and Business Records 1973-2003 MS 3009-RG 27
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Publisher Richard Durrell Files, 1973-1983; 56.25 Linear feet in 57 record cartons
  - Subseries I.B. Subject Files, 1973-1983; 55.25 Linear feet in 56 record cartons
    - Filler Space: Others In People, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 37)
    - Folio, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 38)
    - Food Category, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 39)
    - Fortune, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 40)
    - Fractional Units [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 41)
    - Free Space Requests, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 42)
    - Gallagher Report, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 43)
    - Golf: Sour Mash: May 6-7, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 44)
    - Golf: Time Inc. Invitational; Detroit: June 7, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 45)
    - Golf: Time Inc. Invitational: Maidstone: June 28-29, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 46)
    - Golf: Tuxedo: July 8, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 47)
    - Golf: Time Distribution Services and Retailers: National Golf Links: August 18, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 48)
    - Golf: General Foods Groups: National Golf Links: August 25, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 49)
    - Golf: Time Inc. Golf Outing: Chicago: September 13-14, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 50)
    - Good Housekeeping, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 51)
    - Ideas: People Puzzles, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 52)
    - International, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 53)
    - International: England, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 54)
    - International: Japan, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 55)
    - Leading National Advertisers (LNA), 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 56)
    - Legal, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 57)
    - Legal: Logo, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 58)
    - Legal: Trademark [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 59)
    - Letters: Arthritis Foundation, 1982 (Offsite-box 2992, Folder 60)
    - Letters: Complaints on Edit, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 1)
    - Letters: Complaints Re: Malpractice Edit, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 2)
    - Letters: Complaints Re: Too Much Advertising, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 3)
    - Letters: Kajunski, Billie, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 4)
    - Letters: Miscellaneous, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 5)
    - Letters: Per Person vs. Billing, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 6)
    - Letters: Pricing, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 7)
    - Letters: Reports: Second Half, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 8)
    - Letters: Requests for Edit, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 9)
    - Licensing, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 10)
    - Licensing: French Licensing Proposal, ca. 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 11-14)
    - Life, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 15)
    - Liquor Category, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 16)
    - Little Brown, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 17)
    - Little Brown: Sarah Hall, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 18)
    - Little Brown: Tenth Anniversary Book, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 19)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: With Clients, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 20)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Herb Brooks: March 17, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 21)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Brunch: May 23, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 22)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Knoxville Expo: June 4-6, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 23)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Intrepid: September 16, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 24)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Clare Crawford Dinner: Washington, D.C.: October 14, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 25)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Publisher's Dinner: November 23, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 26)
    - Magazine Commitee, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 27)
    - Magazines, Tabloids, Etc., 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 28)
    - Mailings, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 29-30)
    - Mailings: Book: Man From St. Petersburg, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 31)
    - Mailings: Richard Durrell Book Mailings, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 32)
    - Media Decisions, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 33)
    - Media Industry Newsletter (MIN), 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 34)
    - Media Networks Inc., 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 35)
    - Mediamark Research Inc., 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 36)
    - Meetings: General, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 37)
    - Meetings: Management Task Force, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 38)
    - Meetings: Managers Meeting: March, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 39)
    - Meetings: People Sales Meeting: April 19-22, 1982 (Offsite-box 2993, Folder 40)
    - Meetings: Circulation: Dorset: June 15, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 1)
    - Meetings: Troutbeck: June 22-23, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 2)
    - Meetings: Five Year Strategy Session: August 5, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 3)
    - Meetings: Board Managers Meeting: September 27-29, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 4)
    - Memoranda: Business Office, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 5)
    - Memoranda: Crowley, John, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 6)
    - Memoranda: Crutcher, Larry, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 7)
    - Memoranda: Donovan, Hedley [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 8)
    - Memoranda: D'Onoforio, Pat: Share Of Market Report, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 9)
    - Memoranda: Edit, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 10)
    - Memoranda: Elliman, Don, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 11)
    - Memoranda: Gallagher, John, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 12)
    - Memoranda: Gentalen, Tiit, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 13)
    - Memoranda: Goltra, Libby, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 14)
    - Memoranda: Grander, Haidee: Proposals, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 15)
    - Memoranda: Grunwald, Henry, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 16)
    - Memoranda: Gunn, Larry, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 17)
    - Memoranda: Harris, Bill, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 18)
    - Memoranda: Himmelfarb, Debbie, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 19)
    - Memoranda: Karageorge, Penelope, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 20)
    - Memoranda: Kyle, Bob, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 21)
    - Memoranda: List [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 22)
    - Memoranda: Marketing Services, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 23)
    - Memoranda: McCluskey, Jim, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 24)
    - Memoranda: Meigher, Chris, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 25)
    - Memoranda: Miscellaneous, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 26)
    - Memoranda: Motta, Tony, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 27)
    - Memoranda: Mulcahy, Eileen, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 28)
    - Memoranda: Munro, Dick, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 29)
    - Memoranda: Myers, Bill, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 30)
    - Memoranda: Nunes, Lucy, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 31)
    - Memoranda: O'Brien, Jim, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 32)
    - Memoranda: O'Donnell, Bob, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 33)
    - Memoranda: Owen, Mike, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 34)
    - Memoranda: Promotions, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 35)
    - Memoranda: Publicity, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 36)
    - Memoranda: Roberts, David, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 37)
    - Memoranda: Rolls, Linda: Monthly Report, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 38)
    - Memoranda: Roth, Frank, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 39)
    - Memoranda: Ryan, Pat, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 40)
    - Memoranda: Schiller, Clark [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 41)
    - Memoranda: Serafin, Dick, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 42)
    - Memoranda: Sidey, Hugh, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 43)
    - Memoranda: Stoklos, Mary, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 44)
    - Memoranda: Stolley, Dick, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 45)
    - Memoranda: Sutton, Kelso, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 46)
    - Memoranda: Thomas, Dick, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 47)
    - Memoranda: Znachko, Mike, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 48)
    - Merchandising, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 49)
    - Miscellaneous, 1982 (Offsite-box 2994, Folder 50)
    - Money, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 1)
    - Monthly Reports: Ad Sales, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 2)
    - Movie Category, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 3)
    - Ms. Magazine, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 4)
    - Music Special Issue, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 5)
    - Newsweek, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 6)
    - New Yorker, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 7)
    - New York Times, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 8)
    - Offset: Print Specs, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 9)
    - Orange Coast Magazine, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 10)
    - Order Sheets: Second Half, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 11)
    - Out of Town Schedules, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 12)
    - Parties, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 13)
    - Parties: People Tenth Anniversary, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 14)
    - Parties: Detroit Auto Show: January 15, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 15)
    - Parties: Bob Fisler at "21": January 21, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 16)
    - Parties: Farewell for Dick Thomas: March 3, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 17)
    - Parties: Eighth Anniversary: March 4, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 18)
    - Parties: George Fanning Retirement: March 10, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 19)
    - Parties: Dick Stolley: April 8, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 20)
    - Parties: Philadelphia Penn's Landing; June 17, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 21)
    - Parties: Lunch with Clare Booth Luce: October 21, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 22)
    - People Poll Issue, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 23)
    - People to People, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 24)
    - Permissions, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 25)
    - Personnel, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 26)
    - Personnel: Additions, Space, Thank You's, Etc., 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 27)
    - Photo Exhibits: General, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 28)
    - Photo Exhibit: Boston: February 16, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 29)
    - Photo Exhibit: Washington, D.C.: May 11, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 30)
    - Photo Exhibit: New Orleans: July, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 31)
    - Photo Exhibit: Chicago: September 13-October 2, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 32)
    - Photo Exhibit: Troy, Michigan: October 25-November 13, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 33)
    - PIB, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 34)
    - Presentations: Films, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 35)
    - Presentations: General, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 36)
    - Presentations: Industry [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 37)
    - President's Lunch, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 38)
    - Pricing, Regulations, Tests, Etc., 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 39)
    - Print Order, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 40)
    - Print Order: Plants [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 41)
    - Production, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 42)
    - Profile: Source Simmons, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 43)
    - Progressive Grocer [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 44)
    - Promotion: Air, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 45)
    - Promotion: Circulation Subscription Cards and TV Tests, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 46)
    - Promotion: Consumer Circulation, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 47)
    - Promotion: General, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 48)
    - Promotion: Holland and Callaway, 1982 (Offsite-box 2995, Folder 49)
    - Promotion: Network Television Schedules, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 1)
    - Promotion: New Agency Probe: Consumer Circulation, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 2)
    - Promotion: Radio [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 3)
    - Promotion: Television, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 4)
    - Promotion: Trainee, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 5)
    - Publicity, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 6)
    - Publicity: General, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 7)
    - Publicity: Print, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 8)
    - Public Place, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 9)
    - Publisher's Letter, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 10)
    - Publisher's Lunch, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 11)
    - Radio Radio: Carl Arrington, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 12)
    - Raises, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 13)
    - Rate And CPM Increase, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 14)
    - Rates, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 15)
    - Rates: Subscriptions [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 16)
    - Reader's Digest, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 17)
    - Rebates: Advertising Complaints, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 18)
    - Redbook [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 19)
    - Regional And Metro, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 20)
    - Renewal Space Credit, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 21)
    - Research: Audience Profile, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 22)
    - Research: Business Science International Inc., 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 23)
    - Research: Comparative Readership Study, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 24)
    - Research: Female [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 25)
    - Research: Focus Groups, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 26)
    - Research: Focus Groups: Hartford, Scranton, Charlotte: March 16-19, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 27)
    - Research: Focus Groups: Harrisburg, Toronto, Madison: July 27-30, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 28)
    - Research: Focus Groups: California: October 27-29, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 29)
    - Research: General, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 30)
    - Research: IMS, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 31)
    - Research: Male, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 32)
    - Research: Project: Merle Sprinzen, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 33)
    - Research: Perception Study, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 34)
    - Research: Reader Panel, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 35)
    - Research: Schiller-Schreiber Project, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 36)
    - Research: Teenagers, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 37)
    - Research: Television, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 38)
    - Result Stories, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 39)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Crowley, John, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 40)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Durrell, Dick, 1982 (Offsite-box 2996, Folder 41)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Gallagher, John [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 1)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Gentalen, Tiit, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 2)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Himmelfarb, Debbie, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 3)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Marketing Services, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 4)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Miscellaneous, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 5)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Myers, Bill, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 6)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Promotion, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 7)
    - Screenings: General, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 8)
    - "Search For Alexander", 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 9)
    - "Search For Alexander": San Francisco: February 20-May 16, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 10)
    - "Search For Alexander": New Orleans: June 24-25, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 11)
    - "Search For Alexander": New York City: October 20, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 12)
    - Serialization, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 13)
    - Simmons, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 14)
    - Special Editions, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 15)
    - Special Units, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 16)
    - Speeches: Requests, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 17)
    - Sports Illustrated, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 18)
    - Starch, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 19)
    - Starch: Editorial Scores, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 20)
    - Stars, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 21)
    - Status Report, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 22)
    - Steer Meetings, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 23)
    - Steering Committee: Research Program for Magazines, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 24)
    - Subscriptions, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 25)
    - Subscriptions: Tests, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 26)
    - Supermarket News, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 27)
    - Syndication, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 28)
    - Syndication: Television Proposal: Sandy Frank: April 14, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 29)
    - Technology Committee, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 30)
    - Teletext, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 31)
    - Television and Television Shows, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 32)
    - Test Markets, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 33)
    - Time, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 34)
    - Time Distribution Services: A & P, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 35)
    - Time Distribution Services: Administrative Bulletins, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 36)
    - Time Distribution Services: ADI, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 37)
    - Time Distribution Services: Book and Record Stores, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 38)
    - Time Distribution Services: Checkout, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 39)
    - Time Distribution Services: Clinics, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 40)
    - Time Distribution Services: Correspondence, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 41)
    - Time Distribution Services: Drug Stores, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 42)
    - Time Distribution Services: Front End, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 43)
    - Time Distribution Services: General, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 44)
    - Time Distribution Services: IPDA [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 45)
    - Time Distribution Services: Meetings:, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 46)
    - Time Distribution Services: Meetings: Regional Managers: New York City: March 22-26, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 47)
    - Time Distribution Services: Meetings: Regional Managers: Phoenix: October 10-13, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 48)
    - Time Distribution Services: Meetings: Regional Managers: Atlanta: October 17-20, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 49)
    - Time Distribution Services: Markets, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 50)
    - Time Distribution Services: Newsstand, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 51)
    - Time Distribution Services: Personnel, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 52)
    - Time Distribution Services: Promotion, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 53)
    - Time Distribution Services: Quarterly Market Report, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 54)
    - Time Distribution Services: Racking Stories, 1982 (Offsite-box 2997, Folder 55)
    - Time Distribution Services: Meeting: Regional Managers: December, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 1)
    - Time Distribution Services: Review Recommendation, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 2)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 3)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Jewel Stores, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 4)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Kroger, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 5)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Safeway, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 6)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Super Valu Stores, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 7)
    - Time Distribution Services: Weekly and Monthly Reports, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 8)
    - Time Distribution Services: Wholesalers, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 9)
    - Time Distribution Services: Wholesalers: Charles Levy Circulation Company [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 10)
    - Time Distribution Services: Wholesalers: Late Delivery, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 11)
    - Time Distribution Services: Wholesalers: Late Delivery Reports, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 12)
    - Time/Life Books, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 13)
    - Trades, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 14)
    - Travel Category, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 15)
    - TV Guide, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 16)
    - Universal Product Code (UPC), 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 17)
    - United Way, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 18)
    - Us, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 19)
    - Us: Promotion, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 20)
    - Us: Publicity, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 21)
    - Us: Research, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 22)
    - Us: Sales Report, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 23)
    - Vacations, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 24)
    - Weekly Report: D'Onoforio, Pat, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 25)
    - Weekly Report: Harris, Bill, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 26)
    - Weekly Report: Himmelfarb, Debbie, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 27)
    - Weekly Report: Sutton, Kelso, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 28-29)
    - Wine Category, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 30)
    - Woman's Day, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 31)
    - Woman's World, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 32)
    - Women, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 33)
    - Women's Books, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 34)
    - Year End Issue, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 35)
    - Young & Rubicam Promotion, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 36)
    - Branch Offices: Atlanta, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 37)
    - Branch Offices: Boston, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 38)
    - Branch Offices: Chicago, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 39)
    - Branch Offices: Dallas, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 40)
    - Branch Offices: Detroit, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 41)
    - Branch Offices: Houston [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 42)
    - Branch Offices: Los Angeles, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 43)
    - Branch Offices: Minneapolis, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 44)
    - Branch Offices: New Orleans, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 45)
    - Branch Offices: New York, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 46)
    - Branch Offices: San Francisco, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 47)
    - Branch Offices: Washington, D.C., 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 48)
    - Branch Offices: West Coast (General), 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 49)
    - Branch Offices: Winston Salem: June 10-11, 1982 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 50)
    - Focus Groups: July 6-8, 1983 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 51)
    - Food Marketing Institute: Washington D.C.: October, 1983 (Offsite-box 2998, Folder 52)
- Series II. Assistant Publisher Charlotte Schiff Jones Files, 1973-1978; 1.5 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
  Charlotte Schiff Jones was an assistant publisher at People and former vice president of Manhattan Cable. While Durrell focused on advertising and distribution, Schiff-Jones managed People's marketing, merchandising, and publicity. She produced the short-lived 1978 Time-Life Films People television series broadcast on CBS. The series was meant to translate the People format to television, but was widely panned and quickly canceled in the face of poor audience ratings.
  She had left People and was vice president of marketing at CBS by 1981.
  O'Connor, John. "TV View: On Chats and Chatty Sports Announcers." The New York Times, July 26, 1981. Accessed February 5, 2019. https://www.nytimes.com/1981/07/26/arts/tv-view-on-chats-and-chatty-sports-announcers-john-o-connor.html.
  Prendergast, Curtis, Geoffrey Colvin, and Robert Lubar. The World of Time Inc.: The Intimate History of a Changing Enterprise, Volume Three: 1960-1980. New York: Atheneum, 1986.
  Materials include: People sales memoranda, merchandising materials, correspondence, advertising and weekly reports, circulation numbers, convention information, marketing related materials, and materials regarding the development of the People television show in conjunction with Time-Life Films and CBS.
  Notable correspondents include Richard Durrell, Dick Thomas, Donna Vecchio, and Paul Hale.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Ad Sales, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3041, Folder 1)
  - Ad Sales/Promotion Merchandising, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3041, Folder 2)
  - Advertising Copy Acceptance, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3041, Folder 3)
  - Advertising Free Space Requests, 1978 (Offsite-box 3041, Folder 4)
  - Bermuda: Creative Conference: July 10, 1977 (Offsite-box 3041, Folder 5)
  - Budgets, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3041, Folder 6)
  - Business Office, 1978 (Offsite-box 3041, Folder 7)
  - Circulation, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3041, Folder 8)
  - Circulation: College Market, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3041, Folder 9)
  - Circulation Promotion, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3041, Folder 10)